Subject Files, circa 1985-1992
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Subject Files
circa 1985-1992
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Institution, Assistant Secretary for the Arts and Humanities
SI Records
11 cu. ft. (11 record storage boxes)
Accession 96-006
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records of three projects of the Assistant Secretary for the Arts and Humanities. The majority of the records document the Special Exhibition Fund, established by Office Memorandum (OM) 833 dated October 26, 1984. The OM decreed that the Fund was meant only to fund significant exhibitions beyond the normal financial capability of the bureau, that a published scholarly catalog must be part of each proposal, and that funds were not available for refurbishing of old exhibits. Additional guidelines were adopted by the Special Exhibition Committee in 1985. The Fund was administered through the Assistant Secretary for Museums, then renamed Arts and Humanities, and finally renamed Assistant Provost for Arts and Humanities. These records consist of fund proposals, including budgets, schedules, letters of support, plans for catalogues, CVs, other funding, descriptions, and contingency plans for lesser funding approvals.
Other projects include possible plans for the General Post Office Building adjacent to American Art and Portrait Gallery (AAPG) and the USSR Project, which explored the possibilities of a collaborative exhibition of the US and the USSR on the issues of the 20th century.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Post Office Building (Washington, D.C.); Smithsonian Institution. Assistant Secretary for the Arts and Humanities. Special Exhibition Fund.
Subject
Museums -- Administration.
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Books; Brochures; Manuscripts; Architectural drawings; Audiotapes
- Box 1
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1985-1986
  - Special Exhibition Fund Proposals, 1985 (2 folders) (Box 1 of 11)
  - Special Exhibition Fund Review Meeting, 1986 (Box 1 of 11)
  - Special Exhibition Fund - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 1 of 11)
  - Competition, 1986
  - Gaudi in Context (Box 1 of 11)
  - Dressing the Part (Box 1 of 11)
  - Generations (Box 1 of 11)
  - Birth Rituals (Box 1 of 11)
  - Ebla to Damascus (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Portrait in America (Box 1 of 11)
  - Gene Davis Memorial Exhibition (2 folders) (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Fabric of Life (Box 1 of 11)
  - Art Nouveau Bing (Box 1 of 11)
  - Tropical Forests (Box 1 of 11)
  - Crossroads (Box 1 of 11)
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1987
  - Gigantic Fossil Seabird (Box 1 of 11)
  - Aerospace Computing (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Great War in the Air (Box 1 of 11)
  - The House of Timur (Box 1 of 11)
  - Portraits by Winold Reiss (Box 1 of 11)
  - From Parlor to Politics (Box 1 of 11)
  - How to Become a Fossil (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Peoples and Cultures of Cambodia (Box 1 of 11)
  - Lost and Found Traditions at the National Museum of Natural History (NMNH) (Box 1 of 11)
  - Dynamism and Diversity, the Native Peoples of North America (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Hall of Human Origins (Box 1 of 11)
  - The New Insect Zoo (Box 1 of 11)
  - The Voices of Hellenism (Box 1 of 11)
- Box 2
  - Beyond the Java Sea (Box 2 of 11)
  - Shrimps of the Fisheries Research Vessel (Box 2 of 11)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright (Box 2 of 11)
  - Medieval Art from Yugoslavia (Box 2 of 11)
  - Survey of Smithsonian Collections, Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (SITES) (Box 2 of 11)
  - Science, Power and Conflict (Box 2 of 11)
  - Music in America (Box 2 of 11)
  - Directions (Box 2 of 11)
  - Works (Box 2 of 11)
  - Francis Bacon Retrospective (Box 2 of 11)
  - Perpetual Motif: Man Ray (Box 2 of 11)
  - Hemphill Collection (Box 2 of 11)
  - Masterpieces of American Miniature Painting (Box 2 of 11)
  - American Graphic Arts Series (Box 2 of 11)
  - Albert Pinkham Ryder (Box 2 of 11)
  - King Herod's Dream (Box 2 of 11)
  - Crossroads of Continents (Box 2 of 11)
  - The French Revolution and its Aftermath (Box 2 of 11)
  - The William and Mary Style in Holland, England and America (Box 2 of 11)
  - Great Expectations: Everyday Life in America, 1800-1900 (Box 2 of 11)
  - The Armory Show (Box 2 of 11)
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1988
  - Out-of-Cycle, 1988
  - Experimental Gallery (Box 2 of 11)
  - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (STRI) Photographic Exhibit (Box 2 of 11)
  - Hirshhorn Russian Exhibit (Box 2 of 11)
  - National Zoo: A Photo Album Exhibit (Box 2 of 11)
  - Japanese Art (Box 2 of 11)
  - Rainforest Experiment (Box 2 of 11)
  - Karr/STRI (Box 2 of 11)
  - New Horizons (Box 2 of 11)
  - Futurist National Air and Space Museum (NASM) (Box 2 of 11)
  - Zoo Ark (Box 2 of 11)
  - Portrait Show (Box 2 of 11)
  - American Masterpieces (Box 2 of 11)
  - "The Poetics and Politics of Representation" conference (Box 2 of 11)
  - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (SAO) Proposal (Box 2 of 11)
  - Caribbean Festival Arts (Folders 1-2 of 3) (Box 2 of 11)
- Box 3
  - Caribbean Festival Arts (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 3 of 11)
  - Competition, 1988
  - Josef Hoffmann: Embellishment between Hope and Crime (Box 3 of 11)
  - American Women of the Etching Revival (Box 3 of 11)
  - Legacies of Human Design, Cooper-Hewitt (C-H) (Box 3 of 11)
  - Hiding Out, C-H (Box 3 of 11)
  - Czechoslovakian Architecture and Design (Box 3 of 11)
  - Where on Earth Are You?, NASM (Box 3 of 11)
  - The Try-Out Zone, NMNH (Box 3 of 11)
  - The New Insect Zoo (Box 3 of 11)
  - Seeds of Change (Box 3 of 11)
  - Gigantic Fossil Seabird (Box 3 of 11)
  - Human Origins (Box 3 of 11)
  - The Voices of Hellenism (Box 3 of 11)
  - Interactive Computer Exhibits (Box 3 of 11)
  - Beyond the Java Sea (Box 3 of 11)
  - Life in the Ancient Seas (Box 3 of 11)
  - Plains Indian Art, SITES (Box 3 of 11)
  - Climbing Jacob's Ladder, SITES (Box 3 of 11)
  - Visitor Information Center (Box 3 of 11)
  - Pioneers of Broadcasting in America (Box 3 of 11)
  - Irving Penn (Box 3 of 11)
  - Portraits of Winold Reiss (Box 3 of 11)
  - Hemphill Collection (Application no. 88/23) (Box 3 of 11)
  - Hemphill Collection (Application no. 88/24) (Box 3 of 11)
  - Photography of Invention (Box 3 of 11)
  - William H. Johnson (Box 3 of 11)
  - Pastels of the 1980s (Box 3 of 11)
  - Columbian Exposition (Box 3 of 11)
  - The Boat Show (Box 3 of 11)
  - Promised Land (Box 3 of 11)
  - The Frost Collection (Box 3 of 11)
  - Interpretation for 3 Native American Exhibits, SITES (Box 3 of 11)
  - Field to Factory (Box 3 of 11)
  - Improving Exhibition Interpretation, National Zoological Park (NZP)/NMNH (Box 3 of 11)
  - What Made Photography Popular? (Box 3 of 11)
  - Clocks, Capitalism and Culture (Box 3 of 11)
  - Imagining Yourself (Box 3 of 11)
  - After the Revolution (Box 3 of 11)
- Box 4
  - American Indian Access to Cultural Resources Folklife (Box 4 of 11)
  - Directions (Box 4 of 11)
  - Works (Box 4 of 11)
  - Afro-American Invention and Innovation (Box 4 of 11)
  - Inside Active Volcanoes (Box 4 of 11)
  - Anatolia (Box 4 of 11)
  - The Great American Comic Strip (Box 4 of 11)
  - Immigrant Voices (Box 4 of 11)
  - Archetypes: Five Themes in the Visual Arts of Africa (Box 4 of 11)
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1989
  - Out-of-Cycle, 1989
  - Commerce Department Exhibit (Box 4 of 11)
  - Parting the Green Curtain (Box 4 of 11)
  - Update Video, Natural History Building (NHB) (Box 4 of 11)
  - French Bicentennial (Box 4 of 11)
  - Black Expressive Culture in Philadelphia (Box 4 of 11)
  - Sokari Exhibition (Box 4 of 11)
  - L'Art de Vivre (Box 4 of 11)
  - Deaf Way Brochure (Box 4 of 11)
  - Competition, 1989
  - First Ladies (Box 4 of 11)
  - Public Visitors Center, Whipple Observatory (Box 4 of 11)
  - The Good, the Bad, and the Cuddly (Box 4 of 11)
  - The Art of Bill Reid (Box 4 of 11)
  - Nomads (Box 4 of 11)
  - Seeds of Change (Box 4 of 11)
  - Invertebrate Study Hall (Box 4 of 11)
  - Clocks, Capitalism and Culture (Box 4 of 11)
  - After the Revolution (Box 4 of 11)
  - Exhibition Preview Area, National Museum of American History (NMAH) (Box 4 of 11)
  - From Parlor to Politics (Box 4 of 11)
  - Audio Visuals in Permanent Exhibitions, NMAH (Box 4 of 11)
  - Land of Promise (Box 4 of 11)
  - American Encounters (Box 4 of 11)
  - Rock 'n' Roll (Box 4 of 11)
  - Hands on History Room (Box 4 of 11)
  - Engines of Change (Box 4 of 11)
  - Directions (Box 4 of 11)
  - Works (Box 4 of 11)
  - Culture and Commentary (Box 4 of 11)
  - The Real McCoy (Box 4 of 11)
  - Resources in American Indian Communities, Folklife (Box 4 of 11)
  - Ancient Japan (Box 4 of 11)
- Box 5
  - Chang Dai-chien (Box 5 of 11)
  - Java History Trail (Box 5 of 11)
  - Harvard-SI Partnership in Astronomy (Box 5 of 11)
  - Where Next, Columbus? (Box 5 of 11)
  - American Military Women (Box 5 of 11)
  - The West as America (Box 5 of 11)
  - W. H. Johnson (Box 5 of 11)
  - Hemphill Collection (Box 5 of 11)
  - World's Columbian Exposition (Box 5 of 11)
  - Homelessness, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Coming of Age in America (Box 5 of 11)
  - Exhibition About AIDS (Box 5 of 11)
  - Seeds of Change, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - World Geography (Box 5 of 11)
  - Contrasts, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - The Real McCoy, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Who Wears the Pants, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Where Next, Columbus? (Box 5 of 11)
  - Debate-Oriented Quincentennial Exhibition (Box 5 of 11)
  - Film, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - All Systems Go, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - India Along the Ganges, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Africa Adorned, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Climbing Jacob's Ladder, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - Tokpela, an Exhibit about Hopi Indians, SITES (Box 5 of 11)
  - To Color America (Box 5 of 11)
  - The Intimate World of Alexander Calder (Box 5 of 11)
  - The Cooper Union Legacy (Box 5 of 11)
  - Homage to Niko Tinbergen (Box 5 of 11)
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1990
  - Out-of-Cycle, 1990
  - Evaluation of Volcanoes (Box 5 of 11)
  - Parlor to Politics (Box 5 of 11)
  - Turning Over Old Leaves, Smithsonian Institution Libraries (SIL) (Box 5 of 11)
  - Chamber Music (Box 5 of 11)
  - Crossroads, NMNH (Box 5 of 11)
  - Symposium for Ryder (Box 5 of 11)
  - Deinstallation of the Experimental Gallery (Box 5 of 11)
  - Doghouse (Box 5 of 11)
  - Competition, 1990
  - Freer Gallery Reinstallation Casework (Box 5 of 11)
  - Court Arts of Indonesia (Box 5 of 11)
  - IEI: A Collaborative Project, NZP and NMAH (Box 5 of 11)
  - Palm Court Arcade (Box 5 of 11)
  - The Great Victorian Exhibition (Box 5 of 11)
  - Rehabilitation of Armed Forces Exhibits (Box 5 of 11)
  - Southern Culture and the Emergence of Rock 'n' Roll Music (Box 5 of 11)
  - Youth Interpreter Program (Box 5 of 11)
  - Two Methods of Experiencing Land of Promise (Box 5 of 11)
  - Land of Promise (Box 5 of 11)
  - When Kings Speak: Art and the Discourse of Power in Islamic Art (Box 5 of 11)
- Box 6
  - The Good, the Bad and the Cuddly (Box 6 of 11)
  - Kangaroos, People and the Environment (Box 6 of 11)
  - You Be the Judge (Box 6 of 11)
  - Dubuffet (Box 6 of 11)
  - Works (Box 6 of 11)
  - Four Latin American Pioneers (Box 6 of 11)
  - Rembrandt Peale (Box 6 of 11)
  - Cecilia Beaux (Box 6 of 11)
  - Columbian Exposition (Box 6 of 11)
  - Jewelry of Albert Paley (Box 6 of 11)
  - Chicano Art (Box 6 of 11)
  - The Experimental Gallery (Box 6 of 11)
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1990
  - Competition, 1990
  - Zoomuse (Box 6 of 11)
  - Czech Architecture and Design (Box 6 of 11)
  - Global Image - The Process of Mapping (Box 6 of 11)
  - Donald Deskey (Box 6 of 11)
  - NASM Information Center (Box 6 of 11)
  - Principles of Flight (Box 6 of 11)
  - Where Next, Columbus? (Box 6 of 11)
  - Trust But Verify (Box 6 of 11)
  - WWI in the Air (Box 6 of 11)
  - Museum Support Center (MSC) Photo Exhibit (Box 6 of 11)
  - Seeds of Change (Box 6 of 11)
  - What Does It Mean to Be Human? (Box 6 of 11)
  - Blacks in the US Congress (Box 6 of 11)
  - The Perpetual Campaign (Box 6 of 11)
  - Vietnam (Box 6 of 11)
  - The Real McCoy (Box 6 of 11)
  - The Java History Trail (Box 6 of 11)
  - A Multicultural Portable Traveling Exhibit about the Smithsonian (Box 6 of 11)
  - Anacostia Quincentennial Project (Box 6 of 11)
  - Computer Workstations, NASM (Box 6 of 11)
  - Biopark Initiative (Box 6 of 11)
- Box 7
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1991
  - Out-of-Cycle, 1991
  - Star Trek (Box 7 of 11)
  - Experimental Gallery (Box 7 of 11)
  - Marine Education/Conservation Center (Box 7 of 11)
  - Gender Issues Action Group (Box 7 of 11)
  - Musical History (Box 7 of 11)
  - Journalistic Coverage, World War II (Box 7 of 11)
  - Oceans (Box 7 of 11)
  - Competition, 1991
  - Kangaroos, People and the Environment (Box 7 of 11)
  - Saynday Was Coming Along, Drawings by Silverhorn (Box 7 of 11)
  - Beyond Category: The Musical Genius of Duke Ellington (Box 7 of 11)
  - Coordinated Astronomy Exhibit, SAO (Box 7 of 11)
  - Donald Deskey (Box 7 of 11)
  - Maps: Ways to Read the World (Box 7 of 11)
  - Romare Bearden (Box 7 of 11)
  - The Art of Thomas Cole (Box 7 of 11)
  - American Wicker (Box 7 of 11)
  - Ashcan Artists (Box 7 of 11)
  - World Columbian Exposition (Box 7 of 11)
  - American Musical Theatre (Box 7 of 11)
  - Collection of Dr. Fritz Daguillard (Box 7 of 11)
  - Principles of Flight (Box 7 of 11)
  - Vietnam (Box 7 of 11)
  - Where Next, Columbus? (Box 7 of 11)
  - The Great War in the Air (Box 7 of 11)
  - When Kingship Descended from Heaven (Box 7 of 11)
  - Ancient Japan (Box 7 of 11)
  - Perpetual Campaign (Box 7 of 11)
  - Japanese American Women (Box 7 of 11)
  - Black Land Grant Colleges (Box 7 of 11)
  - World's Fairs (Box 7 of 11)
  - Metro Rail Comes to Anacostia (Box 7 of 11)
  - You Make and Keep History (Anacostia Museum - AM) (Box 7 of 11)
  - Powers and Resonances (Box 7 of 11)
  - The Cold War (Box 7 of 11)
  - Four Latin American Pioneers of Modernism (Box 7 of 11)
  - Spiders (Box 7 of 11)
  - Where Land Meets Sea (Box 7 of 11)
  - Achieving the Nation's Capital (Box 7 of 11)
  - Smithsonian Gallery of Art Competition (Box 7 of 11)
  - Land of Promise (Box 7 of 11)
  - Nikola Tesla (Box 7 of 11)
  - Young Interpreters Program (Box 7 of 11)
  - Revisions to Information Age (Box 7 of 11)
  - Chesapeake Bay/Marine Hall (Box 7 of 11)
  - Benedicte Wrensted (Box 7 of 11)
  - Exhibition Interpretation, NZP (Box 7 of 11)
  - Rhythm and Blues, Folklife (Box 7 of 11)
- Box 8
  - SPECIAL EXHIBITION FUND, 1992
  - Out-of-Cycle, 1992
  - Degenerate Art (Box 8 of 11)
  - Whistler: Image and Icon (Box 8 of 11)
  - Black Mosaic: The Changing Face of Black Life in Washington, D.C. (Box 8 of 11)
  - Red, Hot and Blue (Box 8 of 11)
  - Exhibiting Selves and Others (Box 8 of 11)
  - Powers and Resonances (Box 8 of 11)
  - Workers at the White House (Box 8 of 11)
  - Myths, Monuments and Museums (Box 8 of 11)
  - Maroon Culture in the Americas, Folklife (Box 8 of 11)
  - Science in the Age of Columbus, SIL (Box 8 of 11)
  - Competition, 1992
  - Eva Hesse (Box 8 of 11)
  - Four Latin American Pioneers (Box 8 of 11)
  - Jean Dubuffet (Box 8 of 11)
  - The Presence of Absence (Box 8 of 11)
  - Indus Valley (Box 8 of 11)
  - Joined Colors (Box 8 of 11)
  - 1893 World's Fair (Box 8 of 11)
  - Ashcan Artists (Box 8 of 11)
  - American Daguerreotype (Box 8 of 11)
  - Roy Decarava (Box 8 of 11)
  - Watercolors of Edward Hopper (Box 8 of 11)
  - Jacob Kainen (Box 8 of 11)
  - Alexander Calder (Box 8 of 11)
  - Red, Hot and Blue (Box 8 of 11)
  - Cecilia Beaux (Box 8 of 11)
  - Whistler (Box 8 of 11)
  - James Vanderzee (Box 8 of 11)
  - 1846 (Box 8 of 11)
  - Exotic Illusions (Box 8 of 11)
  - An Ocean Apart (Box 8 of 11)
  - The Power of Maps (Box 8 of 11)
  - Donald Deskey (Box 8 of 11)
  - Smithsonian Achievements, Smithsonian Institution Archives (SIA) (Box 8 of 11)
  - Try This On (Box 8 of 11)
  - Go Forth and Serve (Box 8 of 11)
  - Case-in-Point (Box 8 of 11)
  - Nikola Tesla (Box 8 of 11)
  - Appomattox Courthouse Furniture (Box 8 of 11)
  - Land of Promise (Box 8 of 11)
  - American Encounters (Box 8 of 11)
  - Ethnic Imagery (Box 8 of 11)
  - Masterworks (Box 8 of 11)
  - The Cold War (Box 8 of 11)
  - Vietnam (Box 8 of 11)
  - Soviet Space Exploration (Box 8 of 11)
  - Where Next, Columbus (Box 8 of 11)
  - Black Mosaic (Box 8 of 11)
  - Tunnels (Box 8 of 11)
  - Kangaroos (Box 8 of 11)
  - Forest Stories on the Move (Box 8 of 11)
- Box 9
  - Crossroads of the Continents (Box 9 of 11)
  - Spiders (Box 9 of 11)
  - How Things Fly (Box 9 of 11)
  - The Rise of the Isthmus (Box 9 of 11)
  - Java History Trail (Box 9 of 11)
  - Public Education and Information, SAO (Box 9 of 11)
  - Exhibition for Rural Organizations (Box 9 of 11)
  - Young Interpreters' Program, NMAH (Box 9 of 11)
  - GENERAL POST OFFICE BUILDING (GPOB)
  - Research and Scholars Center, 1992 (Box 9 of 11)
  - Research and Scholars Center - Programs (Box 9 of 11)
  - Save Outdoor Sculpture! (Box 9 of 11)
  - National Museum of American Art (NMAA) intern program (Box 9 of 11)
  - NMAA public programs (Box 9 of 11)
  - American ART NETwork (Box 9 of 11)
  - Functional Space Use Study and Recommended Conceptual Plan, 1983 (Box 9 of 11)
  - Program Requirements and Spatial Analysis, 1986 (Box 9 of 11)
  - Selected documents, 1984, 1988-1989 (Box 9 of 11)
  - Current documents, 1991-1992 (Box 9 of 11)
  - Planning and Development Status Report for the Area Surrounding the GPOB, 1988 (Box 9 of 11)
  - GPOB Technical Potential and Limitations, Phase IV-A, 1991 (Box 9 of 11)
  - GPOB Technical Potential and Limitations, Phase IV-B, 1991 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1984 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1985 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1986 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1987 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1988-1989 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1990 (Box 9 of 11)
  - General, 1991 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 11)
- Box 10
  - USSR PROJECT
  - Soviet/American delegations (Box 10 of 11)
  - Invitations (Box 10 of 11)
  - Drawings to be inserted in summary document (Box 10 of 11)
  - Keens report (Box 10 of 11)
  - Letter of intent between SI and Ministry of Culture, USSR, 1990 (Box 10 of 11)
  - Articles (Box 10 of 11)
  - Gubenko proposal (Box 10 of 11)
  - Budget (Box 10 of 11)
  - US Information Agency (USIA) (Box 10 of 11)
  - Andrea Harris (Box 10 of 11)
  - Logistics (Box 10 of 11)
  - Sturbridge logistics (Box 10 of 11)
  - Other SI Russian projects (Box 10 of 11)
  - Resumes (Box 10 of 11)
  - Secretary's trip report, 1990 (Box 10 of 11)
  - Moscow report - Marc Pachter, 1990 (Box 10 of 11)
  - Correspondence (Box 10 of 11)
  - Fundraising (Box 10 of 11)
  - Travel expenses - USA/USSR Exhibition Planning Team (Box 10 of 11)
  - Delegation ideas (Box 10 of 11)
  - Delegations ideas - Suzdal (Box 10 of 11)
  - Soviet delegation - Suzdal (Box 10 of 11)
  - American delegation - Suzdal (Box 10 of 11)
  - Suzdal meeting (Box 10 of 11)
  - Flam report, 1989 (Box 10 of 11)
  - Plenary Session II (Russian), November 30, 1990 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
  - Plenary Session III (Russian), December 1, 1990 (3 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
  - Audubon Room, November 29-30, 1990 (4 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
  - Audubon Room, December 1, 1990; South Room, November 29, 1990 (4 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
  - South Room, November 30-December 1, 1990 (4 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
  - Board Room, November 29-30, 1990 (4 audiocassettes) (Box 10 of 11)
- Box 11
  - Board Room, December 1, 1990; unlabelled tape (3 audiocassettes) (Box 11 of 11)
  - Fundraising, 1989-1992 (Box 11 of 11)
  - Protocol on working groups (Box 11 of 11)
  - US/USSR 20th Century Project (Box 11 of 11)
  - US/USSR Planning meeting - Telegrams (Fax) (Box 11 of 11)
  - US/USSR Planning Committee; Popov and Mikheeva visit, 1988-1989 (Box 11 of 11)
  - US/USSR Planning Committee, 1989 (Box 11 of 11)
  - Russian Panel (Box 11 of 11)
  - Secretarial panel (Box 11 of 11)
  - Telexs (Box 11 of 11)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 11 of 11)
  - 'DEGENERATE ART:' THE FATE OF THE AVANT-GARDE IN NAZI GERMANY
  - Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 11 of 11)
  - General material (3 folders) (Box 11 of 11)
  - Dinner, November 19, 1991 (2 audiocassettes) (Box 11 of 11)
  - Architectural drawings (Box 11 of 11)